Dhanush Saji

Full Stack Developer



- dhanushsaji1@gmail.com
- **\$547074716**
- Pathanamthitta, Kerala, India
- **1** 06/03/1998
- in dhanush-saji
- Ohanush-Saji
- Dhanush-Saji

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An enthusiastic Full Stack Developer with experience in website hands-on development using the MERN stack and many web technologies such as HTML, CSS, and JS. I'm excited to contribute significantly to the team's success through hard effort, attention to detail, and good organisational abilities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer, Byte Infotech

Jan 2021 – Jan 2022 | Trivandrum, India

- Worked on a project for the Telangana government
- Designed UI with Figma, Adobe XD, leveraging associated models and tools to reduce development time

Freelance Graphic designer

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020

Interests

Guitarist | Singer

Awards

Certificate of Achievement

2020 - Awarded a Certificate of Achievement for developing the project 'KTU Guru'

SKILLS

Technical Skills

ReactJs | Node.Js | JavaScript | HTML | CSS | TailwindCSS | MongoDB | Mongoose | Chakra-UI | GitHub | Open AI | Git | DSA | ExpressJs | Material-UI | Postman | Figma | Bootstrap | C |

Soft Skills

Teamwork | Problem Solving | Remote Work | Proactive | Time Management | Self-learning

PROJECTS

White Feather ∂ ()



White Feather is a women cosmetic e-commerce platform.

Tech - Stack used: ReactJS, Chakra UI

Area of responsibility:

- Login (authentication)
- Navbar

A collaborative project was developed within 5 days with a team of 5 people.

Semrush Clone ⊘ ()



Semrush is a website which offer SEO services, SMM, Content marketing, etc

Tech-Stack used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Area of responsibility:

- Feature page
- Blog page

An individual project was developed within 5 days.

The Little Al ⊘



The Little AI is a website which includes a chatbot that comprehends human speech nuances, responds contextually

Tech - Stack used: ReactJS, Chakra UI, Open AI

Area of responsibility:

- Login (authentication)
- Landing page
- Chat Page

An individual project was developed within 4 days.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development (Full-time), Masai School

May 2022 - Feb 2023

Btech in Computer Science, *College of Engineering, Muttathara,*

July 2016 - May 2020 | Trivandrum

Higher Secondary Education, S.V.G.V.H.S.S

June 2014 - March 2016 | Pathanamthitta

Activities

KTU Guru 🔗

An E-Learning website for Kerala Technical University students

Tech-Stack used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP

Developed an E-learning platform for students under KTU(Kerala Technological University)

Area of responsibility:

- UI/UX Designing
- Graphic Designing

A collaborative project developed within 3 months, with a team of 9.